Hello hello everyone welcome back to my channel
creative friends in today's first video
we discussed the weekly market let's
see all these points news and indicators
like minerals in the video all the indicators
and updates saw right now there has been a
lot of quality in the market in the meantime some of the Nifty
indicators will see good correction and
soil is consistently struggling at some of its long-term tractor
levels
so this bullish trend may remain for the next few days
so we feel
this is the time to take a less anything approach and keep dipping
your office investments a little keeping all
these news and
indicators in mind which fundamentally strong
stocks can be currently undervalued to avoid chopping which stocks
you can
still buy at good valuations and
which festivals can you buy them then we will
discuss that in this video
friends if you haven't subscribed to this channel then do it
now and also press the bell icon
because we keep updating
our voice list like this on a weekly basis without stopping by job
And we keep sharing with you
which can be very useful for you, so without taking any more after wasting
time, let's start with
our first company Britannia from Assam,
we are talking about Britannia Industries, a giant company in India in Bigg Boss
and before starting the whole discussion, let me
remind you once that
this is not a video in which we will do
dipper naman channels of all the staff, here we will take all the
stock tips 13 and their price, we will
talk about it for space, but there are
different divisions, so I have created a favorite
playlist, so you can maintain in
which there is already different ambulance of HDFC Bank ITC
Limited,
watch those videos, you can see
how we will
set the difference detail alarm of all these stocks one by one, you will
understand them and all the
fundamental parameters of the whole business, but we are
not going to do that in this video, this video is
a review, a sale, in which we take
over between the company on the price opportunity,
but if I go for an appointment for the playlist of that fundamental address, then
from there
you can do duty over  We can also take a look at how we will do
detailed research on all these companies, so by
doing that we will go back to the
discussion of today's video in front of our first company
Vrat
Industries, a big problem is our company,
its market place in a criminal
procedure code, comments around it are also quite
turmeric, one person's vague turmeric will be
considered devils, beta tester points
142, for those viewers who are watching our videos for the first time, please
revise something once, this is for the
semester, which tells that that
particular topic is less than the overall market, bolo
time or more order tile, when it is
less than number one, then we assume that that
particular stock is less than the market,
and right now it is more than number one, then we assume that
TikTok over and more votes than the market,
which is egg bhurji companies, scam
news, let's see every clear view, then we
often see
that in pharma, IT, FMCG, all these
directors are conservatives,
actors, defence sector, their
beta is less than 1, some of us here  If the
Britannia Industries appears to be a fake
company, then its beta points are less than 141, which is
less than the market.
Let's talk about the industry's base price of 7172. You are getting the opulence at a very good discount, almost 4950. So, like definitely trading at a discount for the first level and at the top current level, you can start a definitive addition in it. We are going to
talk about at which time
you want to start admission on this occasion or continue it.
If such measures are
discussed, we will talk about the level, we will talk about the conservative level, we will
talk about removing all the leaves immediately.
Now you can see 50% 12%. This shows that
people have withdrawn their long-term investments
in the trading account and have
started taking delivery of long-term interest. At a good level,
when we talk about 12%, its
delivery percentage which is around 2530 percent is
considered quite strong. This very
healthy robust delivery percentage will reach
Britannia Industries.  To do this, the
price of juice will be at 3435,
which is around the current price. So, at
this level, you can see with your eyes that the organization has placed a
stop
on this proposal. So,
definitely a good support level, timing is good.
But if you want to wait a little, then you
can update the price level from 3000 to 310. If you take that into account, then
this company looks different.
It is not a big conference,
it will come again on this channel, but if you
want to wait on it and what ever you
go to, then you can do this lab technician on it
and if you start in 1 minute,
but even under the current price, it is not a
regular service tax meeting. Attend speed.
Our next company is also a different
company.
How many big companies have a market capitalization?
How many big companies were there? 5 lakh and a half lakh
crore. Whose market capitalization is
Daniel, it is quite around one and a half percent. It has diminished to a great extent.
It is
less than Britain, but both
are C companies and they will diminish.  This is also a low voltage
stock. If it is lower than the overall market, then a
very low voltage stock is available at the base of the industry around
724 or something similar around the same industry level at
7273.
And you can see the delivery percentage
here too. The delivery
percentage is quite high. A very strong delivery percentage of
only five rupees will be quite
strong. I think who
knows, 2250 is just a good
quote. If you want to start admission on April 27th, then this is a very
strong
price level. You can see that sir, good
support levels for regulating actuals.
But if you want to wait a little
and now you want to be conservative and restate,
according to the fixed position, then
you can wait for its festival from 2000.
There the level of steel in
Bijnor Shetty will increase further. Can very from this
last step meeting is Uttam on the channel.
Our next company
is a pharmaceutical company. Talking about a French multinational
pharmaceutical company of India, the
left leg is a French company.
We are talking about Indian Subsidiaries of India,
its market is up, it has
a midcap company around 18,000 crore,
duty Anil is quite brilliant and Moses has a
blur of four percent and along with that it also
gives you capital appreciation, money and training for the long term. So if both things are
seen then it is a very good company.
1512 investment from different perspectives. This can be a very
strong candidate. Would be a
tasty point to save. If the market is much
lower than
Torqued, it is quite low. Its computer
overall market industry base is
around 3839 and you are getting a payment of around 3940 at the
same yellow level.
Computer industry average speed is higher than 7568. Very
strong delivery percentage.
This shows that for a long time people have
started with its permission. Address
price love letters pay time. I think that
Akram list in Son of India to start at
7568.780 is its current price,
rather it is very close, but can be very
Promising vitamin A native of that I can now see that
on this occasion, the seeds of this crop have
supported it many times somewhere the rain has
reduced from there and gone up, so that's why
I think this can be a very strong
spicy flavor, so at that time elective, but
if you want to wait a little, it is a mid-cap, then
Agarwal Dilip becomes a
jogging trigger in the market and
because of that, if small-cap stocks, mid-cap
stocks, but body is formed, then
regulation on 1000 7766 price table and also in the
same manner can be started, so on
top of that, from prices to take
medicine of India, our next company is
India Kids Print Company, India's
largest market, Parinda Paint Industry, we are
talking about Asian Paints, its
market pressure has allowed around 2.5 lakh crore,
very big companies, last step, that
it is not a very heavyweight company,
around diminished point five percent, so it will be
considered a bag, this is a Ghosh company, so it does
not do much different, its
density is a little less, you are seeing Bitcoins
for a minute, it is much less than the market  Bilateral
talks are industries at 193, so
all the staff rates of this industry are on highway roads, the
back of the industry is quite high at 193
and you are seeing this at a slightly higher valuation than that,
so
why is it so fundamentally sound? One of the
largest wealth
creators in 25 minutes, every student. So, it is
natural for such companies to get a little cream valuation. So, look here, a
slightly lower version of the industry's position,
you can see
Hussain's delivery percentage, north delivery
percentage is definitely a little low, so at
what price level can you take it, you can
convert Asian Paints on this decision. Let's
talk about that, 25 and 26 levels.
I think that the level of 25 and 26
can be a good initial starting point for a good examination
if you want to invest in stocks.
And I think that the way the
best companies to invest in India,
if you want to invest in it, then
25 and 26 are the fourth levels where  That
you can start accommodating the
initial phase of your investments by
loosening the statement and if
you get that stock at 2122 level,
if such quality comes in the market, if
some such good correction comes, then 2122
level can be an even better principle,
its support level is there too and you can consider
investing there,
so both our labels, message in this also
more computer proof, like your
conviction rate, say Asian Paints, you
can take that West Indies,
which personal part will be
more suitable for investing, the
next company of our disc is about India, this
pharmaceutical company is a multinational company,
now Botox is a less accuracy company, such an
Indian subsidiary is doing it near Airport India,
its market capitalization is
around 30,000, three hundred and fifty crores,
dual quite good, it does quite well,
beta of 1.74%, much less than 12th market, bone
test office, elected president, health of the party,
politics  There is a little
pigmentation on it, it is not a very overvalued
stock, it has a lot of expenses,
if you compare it with the industry then
these are fundamentally very strong
companies, if you
complain about the industry then you are not getting a
solution to a little problem, there is a lot of tumor
on Roshan, the current price is
love 86 per cent, very excellent, very strong
delivery was presented, so it shows that a
lot of people are taking delivery of it in their investment account,
not in trading account, in investment
account, long term insurance,
which is very turmeric,
I think that for investing in About India, the
price is 14000, 14000 and a half, in fact, it is very close,
you can already start investing there,
we had also
sent a notification on our Telegram channel that if you
want to invest in Airport India Win 10, then
here are very promising labels to stock
meeting About India in your investment, if you
want to do a new little wait then 13 6073
level  There could be more problems there,
your level of PM Ashraf will increase a little more
and there you can
start investments for long term examination. Among the
leading companies of distraction,
Nestle, Nestle India's
Indian subsidiary, its market value
in India is one of the largest ever seen
companies, along with its actual market
place is Rs 1 lakh 70 thousand crore, it is a very big
company, David is quite excellent,
almost 2% of 1.94 percent, found left and growth
companies, along with that, such a good salary
DP, Dashrath, that the number on this, how
sound company is, son, this point is, by the way,
much less than the market, types of
industries, pending cases from the tree, 123
oaths and this is getting 108 cloves on the back, it is a
bit expensive to compare to the industry,
but the company is much
stronger than this, so a little bit of its express
evaluation, a little bit of prevention justified as that,
delivery presents of 35 percent  The one
which is the t-shirt pimp does
not show the delivery percentage, people
started its dominance on Spice channel,
I think the
latest current price is 17,000 to 17,500, in fact it is very close,
you can start its admission there,
if you have not already bought a minibus,
then if you want to wait a little, then
15,016 and a half Azarka Lovely has good
support there, you can add its accommodation
and if so, the
next companies of our discussion, Muthoot Finance
Gold, one of the largest companies in India present in the final, is
a very strong in BSC
and excellent fruit, its market
capitalization is around 468 471 road,
civil is also quite good, hills different or
around 1.3 percent, tasty 1.2 percent, now
we have already written in many videos
that such rumors went around PNB, first
chapter
talk to them, their beta is a little high,
you are seeing us,
order tiles are a little more than the market, but  Financial
sector stocks will always have a
beta greater than 1. That's easy for reference. If
you look at IT stocks, defense
stocks, their beta is less than 1. As
you've discussed earlier, all of them had
betas less than 1. But Muthoot Finance,
because it's a factor stock, has a
beta higher than the industry's
premier stock. It's
available at a significant discount. Now, you can see that the
industry's base stock is around 100 percent.
You're getting a significant discount on the back of the protein at
important people. So, it's definitely
trading at a discount to the computer
industry average. 36 percent and a different, reasonable
delivery percentage,
which shows that people have
started buying this stock. I think
1112 alone could be a good price level to invest in Muthoot Finance. It's
more accurate to start. The
staff has backed it at this level many times. So,
please, you're definitely good people to
start.
Settings are open if you want to wait a little
if you feel that there could be a slight correction in the stock,
disaster free number for face, then the
level of 9.50 to 1000 can increase good pressure,
then reach from the tractor price, if that
preserve profit is obtained, then this definite
stock meeting in the same manner at a fashionable
patient discussion, the next company is Depositories
paint maker only in India, it is
global level one of the largest
manufacturer of employees under the world, in the whole
world it makes almost 1667 percent
of all the pain killers appear in the
world, in which lottery, similarly
fifty percent of all global
manufacturing of cost syrup is made only,
so this topic discussion was discussed in more detail
in Best of Indore Pharma Sector,
Best of Foreign
Investment in Pharmaceutical Sector, its
detailed discussion was done in it by capturing that video
and you can get a little realization that
why I like Bigg Boss so much, then the
market of this company  Capitalization is around
95,944 products
posted in 11.45 to 0.5 cm, so
less than the market, on let's talk, the industry is
getting around 3140 or a slightly looser version, but the delivery is
so good, you can see that the
delivery percentage is 22%, which shows that
people have started taking delivery of it in their investment work during the long
term investment period,
I think that the level of 34 and
35 can be a very good starting
point, fundamentalist office company affair,
companies from the market, its pension
researchers, so such a strong company will
not have to wait much time,
but still I think that you can see
that 38 and 39 squares were reached, after a
good deviation from there,
after a good consolidation, updates are
getting good price values, around 34 and 35 fourth level, you
can start investing in detox water, but
if you wait a little  Wants to get 21 jobs from home, you
can start
these, we are leading the next companies,
medication
Shahrukh Khan and actress Preeti,
small companies in chemical companies, small cap companies
but fundamentally very sound companies,
its products are very good, it
spreads a lot in the market,
but fundamentally very good companies,
we have discussed it in the Talks for
Investment in Chemical Sector video, you
can see the office discussion in a better way in that video, then
and counting, market capitalization is
around seven and a half thousand crores, definitely
a point company, there is no deposit, so how
small car companies are included in their group is
also not depending much,
hence its fog is a little less, but
as the company grows, it rates
its market city, so
accordingly its delivery can be, but
this criminal is a little less because of this
pond near the company limited, to observe, not
less than the market, say time, stock
investors' extra specific, a little
premium vibration, then definitely getting  It is
good how it is available for free at a valuation
but fundamentally it is a very soft
company so you should give this cream to Western in a holistic manner
thanks to why it is being given prevention
and submit 70% you can see
how strong the delivery percentage is
people have started taking delivery of it in full I will
show you in my control 2425 its
price level is good price
reduced at that time in waiting for
organic which we have been discussing in the last two-three processes and since then
prices
are consolidating so you definitely have opportunities here
you can start a
meeting and this is priceless but if you
want to wait a little and Turkey
is a small cap so if any correction
comes in it then the price label of 18 years 2019
or maybe two scans from above 1819 very
attractive price tag bloody mary
discussion leading company a multinational
pharma city company very strong
multinational pharmaceutical company pfizer
affair  The market capitalization of the company is around
22 crores. You can see its yield is
around seven percent and I am at 67 per cent.
So, in this FD period, you
get so much comment. Even in this period,
you do
not get such a difference in the same amount from any other bank
and you get such a strong difference.
This company has taken this and with
capital appreciation, the price of it is a very
good company. Its office is from giving
benefits. So, it trades
much lower than the market. This topic, as we have discussed later, the
price of pharma stocks is less,
that is visible here
around the baseline price of the industry. You are
not getting it at a very high PM valuation of 2014. The
current price table and to-do
list have been taken. 2009 20x only on
premium calculation of 5 per cent
delivery with very strong
delivery percentage for admission.
I think that Shyam can
get a good admission by taking an offer of 4748 and a half rupees.
Any want  To start your comment in phase
if this top is found near 4041 level,
forces and paper tractor can follow and it can be
at an even more attractive price
there you can start it like this,
leading company of depression ICICI Lombard General
Chanakya Largest Private Player in
India itself but most fundamental and
company, we are talking about its market
application is 100 grams butter, it is
also known as general insurance,
its market place is
around 65 thousand crores, it is a very low
growth company, then its difference is a
little less, your processor is investing in
pension sector stocks, you must have
seen that their demand is not very high, that is what
we can see here,
despite the financial sector factor, you
can see that its target appointment
is less than 121, thickness less than the market, as soon as we look at the channel of 100,
in the financial sector also, the stocks of life
insurance sector or general insurance
sector can be seen, their price  It is a
little less, it is a little quality than the market,
that is what we are seeing here, the
interest is 2014 you are
getting some prevention on the back of 34 but
Saint Lucia on sixty two has a delivery percentage of 2%
this shows that people have started
competing with it and I
think that for 13 and a half to 14 years you can
roast it well, some
time minute
obscene number now you can see that it had
reached the level of sixteen and a half, sixteen hundred and fifty
but from there after a little different correction
you are getting good consolidation on loans,
if you also look at the current price table a
little  If you want to wait, then level up to 1213
is an even better attractive price, that can happen,
you can see that the stock has
support many times on that, on this channel, rise, thank
you, very strong price level and you to
stock meeting is also bid, description of our
next and last companies of depression
that Gujarat State Petronet
Limited GSPL can be
considered a midcap company, borderline scheme
architect presses around 11,000,
eleven and a half thousand crores, can be
considered a company between small cap and midcap,
Daryl is quite good, point not more than one
person's growth, then it will
not be considered diminished to a great extent, if it is a son of birds, then
bililateral tokes are less than the market, it is a
very big company in the distribution and transmission of gas distribution, city gas distribution, CNG, compressed natural gas, CNG partner sex,
its business in Gujarat is
quite good, you
can consider it a monopoly business, there is industry in that region and
you, it
around 10:30  Around 10.5 and it is
getting around the back of the industry, it is getting at 1.5 back, so a
lot of decently valid
companies, a very good Bollywood company,
not a velvet company and the mode 60% to 12%
shows that people have started investing in it at a good level of
dominance.
I think that the price
between 198 and 205 to invest in this pen can vary from it's
impossible, you can see almost too much, it has
reached by reporting from only fat, covering everything,
but from there again there is an Addison correction
and on this occasion it has
also taken support many times, so I think that
this price is definitely a good price,
reduced at admitting to start
investing in JSP. Are you taken, if you
want to wait a little, if you want to be a little
conservative and rest a little wait for the
market correction, then you
can update 175 to 0.5 inches, there
your merger will move towards there  You can
start investing in this in more aggressive minor forms.
Fundamentally, it is a very good company. Pensioners'
Office is a Congress company.
Therefore, it does not get a very high valuation,
but its fundamental performance is
very good. Using financial ratios,
its business, which is a very monopoly business, has a
good growth outlook in that process. That is
why I like this stock.
Its structure is good.
After considering all these factors, I feel
that its performance can be better than its protein in the future.
So if you
want to invest in stocks, if you like this best
friend work of effect, then you can
start investing in these 10 top depending on your
comfort level. You can
also click on more computers in these two price voice messages. You
can invest in the office there, but I hope that all these
discussions on the missions will be helpful to you
and I hope that all these
discussions on computers are about 11-12 computers,
why everyone has it. The only thing is that if you
invest in all your companies  If you are interested in these
sectors or want all the cutting-edge updates and
reviews, then please let me know in the comments
so that we can keep reviewing them in more detail. If you like
your ideas from all the fundamentals, terms of Vipin, it will help you
in creating your investment framework
and will prove to be
very helpful in keeping your thought process updated for long term investors. Friends, I
hope all this information is magic. So friends, this is the video of grass
which is Knowledge Power Screen. This is the
mission of the channel which is to bring the right knowledge to you.
In the upcoming new videos, we will
discuss many interesting topics
and I will keep bringing you useful collides and
topics. Similarly, Ali Khan, we will keep
discussing weekly market updates and our views, doctor, collect market situation. So,
this is definitely a must subscribe to our
channel. Gmail post to your friend. If
you liked today's video content, then
like the video. If you think that this mission
can help someone, then share it with your
friends and family members and
subscribe to the channel. See you in your next
video.  I am part of the discussion with you till then
take care see you soon bye